watchonlineseries.eu 2012-09-23

# Privacy Policy

Never trifle with privacy… Consequently, WatchOnlineSeries.eu takes the confidentiality of your personal information into account. Hereinafter, you will find a record that can help you understand which data we collect, how we gather it, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may share it. Predominantly, there is picked non-personal information that allows us to know how the website works, such as statistical and other analytical data from an aggregate basis of all visitors to WatchOnlineSeries.eu.

Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

WatchOnlineSeries.eu doesn’t lay its visitors under the obligation to become members. However, if you choose to create an account and voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (PII), such as your name and email address, we will ask you to create a user name and password. Only you are liable for maintaining the confidentiality of your registration information. Moreover, you can delineate a personal profile that can be viewed by other members. Our users have the right to update, rectify or even delete their profile anytime.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)

Your Internet protocol address and information associated with your computer like the type of browser (such as “Mozilla Firefox version X” or “Internet Explorer version X”) and the type of operating system (as it were Windows or Macintosh) that you use, the date and time you pay us a visit and the Web pages that you flick through on our site rank among the non-personally identifiable information (Non-PII) we may collect. In order to provide you with a better experience, when you visit WatchOnlineSeries.eu, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This helps us improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can configure your browser to refuse them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Although you choose not to receive cookies, you can still use most of the features of our website.

Disclosure

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to your data. WatchOnlineSeries.eu will not intentionally disclose personally identifiable information in your account except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell, rent or share personal information about you with other people or companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested. WatchOnlineSeries.eu may share with third parties only non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. However, we reserve the right to access and disclose your personal information to government agencies or other parties whose requests we reasonably consider to be justified in order to prevent or take action regarding illegal activities or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of our users or the public, violations of WatchOnlineSeries.eu’s terms of use, as required or permitted by law.

Email

Email addresses are used for password checking, making new friends, for general communication and to send you notifications. WatchOnlineSeries.eu’s users have the possibility to search for other members using the first and last name, email address, text searches and other attributes. By storing these email addresses, we facilitate the communication between our users. We will not use email addresses for other purposes than those described above.

Links to Third Party Sites

WatchOnlineSeries.eu contains links to other websites. However, this statement only covers the website that we own and control. It does not spread over links from WatchOnlineSeries.eu to other third party websites and accordingly, any information collected by the parties who own and control those websites or their use of cookies. Please be aware that each owner operates his own policy regarding the use and sale of personal information and the use of cookies.

Security

We take great care to ensure the security of this website. WatchOnlineSeries.eu has put in place suitable procedural and technological measures meant to protect your data from loss, unauthorized access or malicious attacks, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. They are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including deprivation and even criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. Those being said, you can provide personal information with complete peace of mind.

Policy Changes

WatchOnlineSeries.eu may update this privacy policy. We will inform you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing an office action on our site.
